webctor.com 2013-04-30

# Privacy Policy - Webctor.com

**EFFECTIVE DATE: 10 OCTOBER 2011.**

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

  1. We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.

  2. We do not share your contact information with another User without your consent.

  3. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology.

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal and other information we receive from Users of the Site.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of the Site.

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use. By continuing to use the Site after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the home page of the Site, you are consenting to these changes.

You willingly provide us certain personal information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the Site. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, you should not become a User of the Site.

**The Site and third party sites**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Site. The Site may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by the Owner. The Owner has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release the Owner from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party site to which this Site may be linked.

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the services and specific tools offered within the Site and the related features, to administer your subscription and to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. Below are the types and categories of information that we collect.

**Account**

You may use some of the functionality of the Site without registration, however in order to access some features or other elements of the Site, you will have to create an account. If you use the Site without creating an account, the only information we collect will be non-identifying information related to the use of cookies or web beacons. When creating your account you benefit from number of different services we provide. In this respect you are required to provide the following information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge are personal information allowing others, including the Owner, to identify you: username, email address, password chosen by you, city/state, and in case you are a professional your name, surname and specialization. It is important that you must keep your account password secure and confidential. We do not require you to submit us any personal information concerning your health, like information about medicines you take or diseases you have. If you provide us with such an information you recognize and expressly acknowledge that you do this on your own discretion. We may also ask you to provide additional information after you register if you want to obtain additional services or information or to resolve complaints or concerns. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of any personal information you submit. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using the Site and tools and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Inviting friends**

If you like to tell a friend about the Site, we will ask you for your name, your email address and your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him/her to visit the Site. We do not use your name, your email address or your friend's email information for any other purpose. We will only use the information you provide to send the email you request.

**Forums, message boards, Q &A, groups, etc.**

When you post any message to a forum, message board, Q&A, group or any other public forum within the Site where User can post his/her observations and comments on designated topics, your basic information will be available for all registered Users to see. This basic information consists of your username, or name and specialty in case you are a specialist. You should not post any information about you or any other person to a forum, message board, Q&A, group or other public forums within the Site if you want to keep such information private or you are required by law to do so. Information you post to public forums within the Site is considered public information and may be used by us and third parties. As with any public forum on any site, this information may also appear in third party search engines like Google, Yahoo, MSN etc. We do not control the information indexed and cached by search engines.

**P** **rivacy settings**

We allow you to set the privacy settings for some of the personal information you provide. You can set the privacy setting to private, public, or friends only. Public information can be seen by everybody without limitation. Viewers do not have to be registered Users in order to view this information. Friends only information can be viewed by other registered Users that you have elected to add as a friend. Private information can only be seen when logged in under your username or by the Owner. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information or information concerning your health in any public forum within the Site.

**Log Data**

When you visit the Site or use its functionalities, whether as a registered or a non-registered User our servers automatically record information about your use of and your visit to the Site ("Log Data"). The Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what software you were using, the web page you were visiting immediately prior to visiting the Site, pages of the Site you visited, the time spent on those pages, information you searched for on the Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and for the Site's technical administration, to improve the functionality of the Site and User-friendliness, and to better tailor it to Users' needs.

**Cookies**

Like most sites, the Site uses cookies and web log files to track the Site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows us to recognize you as a User when you return to the Site using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use the Site properly. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the Site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you have logged in to your account. The next time you visit the Site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the Site.

Additionally, if you log out of the Site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing User preferences and tracking User trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the Site, the certain areas within this Site or its services properly. We do not store personally identifiable information in the cookies.

**Web B** **eacons**

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

To deliver these ads properly, the Site may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by the Site so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other sites.

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other sites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. We do not provide personally identifiable information to any advertiser or any other third party.

**Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer**

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Site. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Site services. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

**Communications**

We will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the Site or through other means available through the Site, including text and other forms of messaging. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of material changes of this Privacy Policy or for user service purposes). If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). Please be aware that you may receive certain emails from the Owner related to the proper functioning of your account. You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and amending your email notification choices. By clicking "Sing Up" during the registration process, you also consent to receive commercial or marketing messages from the Owner and/or its partners.

**Sharing i** **nformation with third parties**

We take the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated anonymous information about the usage of our Site to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on the Site.

**Teaming with third parties**

We allow other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

**Legal disclaimer**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the Owner or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

**Disclosures to others**

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of the Owner’s division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell our assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

**Phishing**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the Owner. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**Aggregate information and non-identifying information**

We may share aggregated information that does not include personal information and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal information.

**International transfer**

Your information may be transferred to "and maintained on" computers or servers located outside of your state/country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer.

**Links to other sites**

Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's web site. The fact that we link to a web site or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect information or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit.

**Accessing and changing your account information**

You can review the information you provided us and make any desired changes to them, or to the settings for your account including your email at any time by logging in to your account on the Site. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, we may, for a time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or archival copies of our database. We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by emailing us at support@webctor.com.

**Deleting your account**

You can also delete your account, in which case you can still use the Site, but we may not be able to provide certain services to you. If you delete your account, we may retain certain information contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable information, account recovery, or if required by law. In order to delete your account please visit “Delete Account” section associated with your account.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our servers.

Any information you provided in any forum, message board, Q&A, group or any other public forum within the Site will not be deleted.

**Y** **our obligations**

As a User, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations:

  1. You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.

  2. You must not upload, post or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic. 

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by the Owner, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the Site and the services which it offers.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you use the Site after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our Site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

**Security**

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal information" (as defined in applicable laws related to security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with: (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement; or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

**Data** **retention policy**

We may retain your account information indefinitely, regardless of whether you have disabled your account on the Site. We will retain Log Data consistent with applicable legal requirements. Generally, at a minimum, we will retain the Log Data collected from you in our active, internal company databases for six months, at which point we will migrate such Log Data to our offline archival systems, where we will retain the Log Data for a period of three years (together, the "Retention Period"). After the Retention Period, we will purge the Log Data from our systems. In the event of an investigation by law enforcement or a response to claims or legal process, we may retain the Log Data until such investigation or process is completed, which may be longer than the Retention Period.

**Statement**

The data controller of your personal information is the Owner, i.e. Red Sky Sp. z o. o., a company incorporated under the laws of Poland, with its registered office in Szczecin, at Rynek Sienny 4b Street, Szczecin 70-542, Poland, registered in the entrepreneurs register conducted by the National Court Register maintained by the District Court in Szczecin, XIII Commercial Department, with KRS number 0000209107, NIP number (tax identification number): 642-26-83-651, REGON number 276822679, amount of the share capital of PLN 937.000,00 covered in whole. .

The Owner hereby declares as follows:

  1. All personal information provided will be processed in order to allow the use of the Site.

  2. All personal information transferred to the Owner will be stored by the Owner in its database.

  3. All personal information transferred to the Owner will processed in accordance with the provisions of the Polish Act of 18 July 2002 on providing services by electronic means, as well as in accordance with the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the Protection of Personal Data.

  4. The Owner shall ensure the safety of Users’ personal information and the Owner has implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures as set forth in the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the Protection of Personal Data and has met the requirements specified in the provisions referred to thereof , in particular to protect the personal information to be processed against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of personal information over a network, and against all other unlawful forms of processing. These measures ensure a level of security appropriate to the risks presented by the processing and the nature of the information to be protected having regard to the state of the art.

  5. You have the right to verify, review and correct your personal information processed by the Owner, which also requires you notify the Owner any changes thereof. The right can be exercised by you independently introducing changes in your account or by sending a relevant request at the following address: support@webctor.com.

  6. You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal information, giving the Owner a notice to that effect. Though you provide your personal information to the Owner voluntarily, refusal to provide them renders entry into the agreement with the Owner and access to the Site impossible.

  7. The Owner shall have the right to disclose the personal information only to the authorities entitled under the provisions of the law in force (e.g. a court, the police), in cases specified in the Terms of Use and resulting from the law in force.

  8. The Owner fulfills all the requirements of the Polish Act of 29 August on the Protection of Personal Data. 

  9. After reviewing the above Privacy Policy, by using the Site, especially by clicking "Sign Up" during the registration process, you hereby:

        1. Consent to the processing and use by the Owner all the personal information provided to the Owner, including information obtained as a result of your use of the Site, for the following purposes:
          1. registration in the Site (possibility of using the functionalities offered by the Site);
          2. processing complaints;
          3. replying to correspondence sent by contact form or an e-mail;
          4. technical operation of the Site;
          5. maintaining the Site statistics;
        2. Consent to transfer of your personal information abroad, and in particular to Owner’s affiliated companies or associated entities, or to Owner’s parent company with their registered office outside the Poland, for the purposes of processing in computer systems belonging to the Owner and its business partners. You understand that the above entities may be located in countries that do not guarantee the same level of personal information protection as the level guaranteed in your state/country.

        3. Agree that your consent remains valid for the entire period of your use of the Site.

        4. Declare and confirm that you have read Terms of Use, you understand them and you will comply with them, both in its current wording and with any later amendments.

**How to contact us**

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@webctor.com](mailto:support@webctor.com).
